{
    "subject": "resource/Ex_Machina_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/distributor",
    "object": "resource/Universal_Studios",
    "human_readable": "The distributor of the film Ex Machina is Universal Studios.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9175422787666321,
            "question": "Besides Ex Machina, what other films might Universal Studios have distributed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9119280576705933,
            "question": "Who distributed the film Ex Machina?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.856945812702179,
            "question": "What is the name of the studio that distributed Ex Machina?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.848185658454895,
            "question": "Is Universal Studios involved in distributing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8419129848480225,
            "question": "Which film was distributed by Universal Studios?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8365164399147034,
            "question": "Name a film distributed by Universal Studios."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7835893034934998,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Universal Studios and the film Ex Machina?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6679710745811462,
            "question": "Is Universal Studios known for distributing specific types of films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6252412796020508,
            "question": "Can you give an example of another film distributed by Universal Studios?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39956578612327576,
            "question": "What role does a distributor play in the film industry?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The distributor of the film Ex Machina is Universal Studios.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4661_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give an example of another film distributed by Universal Studios?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4661_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Universal Studios known for distributing specific types of films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4661_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the relationship between Universal Studios and the film Ex Machina?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4661_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4661_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4661_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4661_158.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4661_159.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4661_162.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4661_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4661_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4661_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4661_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4661_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me explain why:\n\nThe documents state that A24 Films acquired the U.S. rights to \"Ex Machina\".  Universal Studios is not mentioned as the distributor in any of the provided texts. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that there is no mention of Universal Studios being the distributor of the film Ex Machina in any of the provided documents. In fact, A24 Films is mentioned as the distributor of Ex Machina in two of the documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4661/re-ranker-msmarco/70.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4661/re-ranker-msmarco/154.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: None of the provided documents mention that the distributor of the film \"Ex Machina\" is Universal Studios. In fact, the documents indicate that it was distributed by A24 Films."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "there is no mention of Universal Studios being the distributor for Ex Machina in any of the provided context information.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "A24 Films acquired U.S. rights to the film Ex Machina.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "the distributor of the film Ex Machina is A24 Films, not Universal Studios.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context clearly states that A24 Films has acquired U.S. rights to the film \"Ex Machina,\" not Universal Studios.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}